<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Health Mate</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello Home fragment</string>
    <string name="profile_image_description">Profile Image</string>

    <string name="open_nav">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="upload_icon_description">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="appointment_button_description">Book an Appointment</string>
    <string name="patient_avatar_description">Patient Description</string>
    <string name="enter_your_concerns">Enter your concerns</string>
    <string name="lbl_appointment_history">Hospital will assign you doctor and notify with the doctor details in the Appointment History within 2 hours. Chances that your appointment time will move within that our according to doctor availability.</string>
    <string name="lbl_HospitalNote">Note: Hospital and doctor have rights to reschedule or cancel your appointment, but do not worry before doing that you will recieve call from hospital. </string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Update Profile</string>

    <string name="lblHospitalOverView">Overview</string>
    <string name="lblHospitalDesc">Welcome to Health Mate, the place where devoted service and caring care meet. We take great satisfaction in creating an atmosphere of warmth, compassion, and unwavering support for each and every one of our patients at this prestigious facility.\n\n Our committed team of healthcare specialists is the first step in our dedication to your well-being. Not only are all of our employees highly qualified in their respective fields, but they also sincerely care about your well-being. You\'ll notice a difference in our level of concern and kindness the moment you walk through our doors. \n\nTime and the well-being of our patients are our top objectives. Since every person\'s path to wellness is different, we customize our services to fit your specific requirements. Our state-of-the-art facilities and advanced medical equipment guarantee that you will get the best possible care. \n\nWhat sets Health Mate apart is our steadfast commitment to providing every client with exceptional service. Our priorities are your comfort and contentment. Every interaction with us should be uplifting and comforting, and that is our goal. The situationWe appreciate you selecting the Health Mate App. \n\nPut your trust in us about your health, and allow us to accompany you on your journey to a better and healthier life.</string>
    <string name="choose_your_role">Choose your role</string>


</resources>